字幕为自制
字幕样式来自EQCN
翻译来自@超菜小咸鱼
本字幕采用知识共享-署名-相同方式共享 4.0 国际许可协议进行许可
http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/deed.zh
I'll be the toast of the town, the girl on the go
我是名利场新秀 社交的名流
I'm the type of pony every pony, every pony should know
我的气质让所有小马 所有小马追求
I'll be the one to watch, the girl in the flow
作为全场焦点 我引领潮流
I'm the type of pony every pony, every pony should know
我的名声让所有名流 所有名流追求
Becoming as popular as popular can be
变得更加出色 让名声无可比
Making my mark, making my mark in high society
不必害怕 在上流社会留下痕迹
I'm the belle of the ball, the star of the show, yeah
我是聚会明星 舞会的王后
I'm the type of pony every pony, every pony should know
我的气质让所有小马 所有小马追求
See how they hang on every word that I speak
看他们对我的话上心不已
My approving glance is what they all seek
我的赞许令他们着迷
I'm the crème de la crème, not just another Jane Doe
我是好中之好 比优秀更优秀
I'm the type of pony every pony should know
我的名声让所有小马追求——
At home, at the opera, on a fancy yacht
在家 在剧院 或在游艇上
Becoming the talk, the talk of all of Canterlot
名气更多 更多就在这坎特洛
I'm the crème de la crème, not just another Jane Doe, yeah
我是好中之好 比优秀更优秀
I'm the type of pony every pony, every pony should know
我的名声让所有小马 所有小马追求
Because I'm the type of pony
他们喜欢我的魅力
Yes, I'm the type of pony
我的姿态和美丽
Yes, I'm the type of pony every pony should know
我要成为 成为货真价实的名流